In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard, the
market cap of the company is ₹57,499 crore,
pinpoint 33, the company makes a difference of zero
percent and the company has around ₹
250 crore and the company has a reserve of ₹
227 crore and the return on
equity of the company, like
and
subscribe and if we talk about shares, tomato
puree is
50%
and public and
now the profit of the company is ₹
6149 crore, loot ₹1193 crore, ₹1473 crore, ₹1271
crore, this time the profit motive of the company has been
seen
and here you can see that the company is going to
give a dividend of ₹5, the date of the company
is 28th July and the record date is ₹15, that is, if
you buy the shares of this company before 28th July, then
you will get a doubt
and here you can see
subscribe 1370
and at this time the share price is ₹1164 and ₹
11 in the share  There is a support of ₹100 and at this time
RSS is nutritious and good
in this exam and this share had gone up to 1670, at this
time discount is available, if you
want to buy in this company then you
can buy it for 1100 rupees and
if you want to buy for diet then
you have two days time today and tomorrow,
if you buy in this share
then you will become a
partner for dividend, that's all in this video,
if you liked the information given in the video then
like and share the video
and subscribe to our channel.